

Contact

+2349098648913

paulrichardevs@gmail.com

Ilorin, Nigeria

Education

2018 - Present

Geography

University of Ilorin

Skills

TS Typescript

React

*TailwindCSS

Next.is

UHTML

GCSS

MongoDB

Firebase

Languages

Yoruba - Native

English - Fluent

Interests

Programming

Reading

MGaming

Paul Richard

Front-End Developer

About

Well-qualified **front-End web developer** familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages with excellent technical abilities offering over **2+ years** of related experience. Proven experience developing consumer-focused web-apps using **Typescript**, **React**, **Next.js**, **HTML**, and **CSS**.

Work Experience

Boreal Coffee - Frontend Developer

OCT 2022 - JAN 2023 | US - REMOTE
I re-created the frontend of Boreal Coffee's official web app using React and Typescript. It was a great experience for me to build the entire frontend.



UpWork - Freelance Developer

JAN 2022 - PRESENT | LAGOS, NIGERIA

Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery. Creating beautiful web and mobile applications using Angular, React, React native and javascript for clients all around the world.



FIT ME - Frontend Engineer

JAN 2023 - FEB 2023 | ILORIN, NIGERIA

Designed responsive websites for gym startup company also redesigning their website from scratch using the frontend tools I know.

